http://aztechsoft.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). Please read on if you wish to learn more about our privacy policy.
What Information do we collect?
We keep only the information about how you have navigated our website. We temporarily keep information on the products you have added to your basket. We do not keep any personal information that would identify you in the future. When processing your order at Amazon there are other details that will be required - see the relevant Amazon Privacy Policy for full details.
We also record usage data such as the pages visited. This information is completely anonymous.
If you sign up for our Newsletter, we will ask for your email address. You can unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time.
How do we protect your information?
Any information we hold is secured in accordance with our internal security policy.
Do we use cookies?
We use cookies to enable you to hold the content of your shopping basket between visits and to record anonymous traffic data. We do not store any personally identifying information in these cookies.
Will we sell your information?
We do not sell any information about their customers; as simple as that. We will not forward your details on to any third party at any time.
Shop Design References
Hydrology, Floodplains and Hydraulics (0)
Roadway, Paving Design (6)
All Products
Shop CAD equipment
Scales and Rulers (3)
All Products
Shop GPS Equipment
Handheld GPS (4)
All Products
Shop Old Time Drafting
Compass and Dividers (4)
All Products
Newsletter
